[Music]
Hey aunty, was he the one with the loan?
Who is the one with the loan?
Wait, wait, wait,
who are you people? You have been
roaming around with a loan for the last six months
and you ask, who are we, the loan makers?
Pay the loan.
Today everyone has come along and we have brought the doctor along with us.
[Music]
[Praise]
So who's coming quickly, everything did
n't work today, I saw Baba Ji having
dangerous people, the affair with a woman,
everything didn't work today, after some time the police also came, the
policeman doesn't support you and he would have supported
me,
oh Baba Ji, where are you going, I am going, I will do
penance on Mount Kailash, there I will
not get into trouble with the police, friend,
oh my god, oh doctor ji, oh where are you going,
yes, we will not get into all that trouble,
all the doctors were fine in Goa, they will earn their living in the
morning,
oh my god, everyone is leaving me.
They are doing very wrong.  You are doing something very wrong.
You will have to pay dearly for this.
Catch me.  No,
yes, there
is some crowd here.
Inspector sir, these people robbed us.  The loot was sold and the
house was left waiting.
Inspector sir, please beat me,
these people have robbed me of my respect and are standing there.
Zebel crushes.  He also wants to make a video and make it viral.
Okay, you wait, we will apply Section 376 on you right now.
You wait, there are
and since Mani Saheb is already trapped, let's get
him inside.
Oh
[laughs]